Guide to the Thomas C. Wilson, Class of 1929, Sheffield Scientific School, Yale University, Photographs of Yale
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Thomas C. Wilson, Class of 1929, Sheffield Scientific School, Yale University, Photographs of Yale
1926-1927
RU 636
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.25
(2 boxes)
The materials consist of photographs of Yale University taken by Thomas C. Wilson. Includes "snapshots of the Yale scene" and photographs of Yale buildings.
Wilson, Thomas Cluff, 1907-
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-A (YRG 46-A), Records and materials broadly documenting Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
Arranged by subject.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of photographs of Yale University taken by Thomas C. Wilson. Includes "snapshots of the Yale scene" and photographs of Yale buildings.
College buildings; New Haven (Conn.) -- Pictorial works; Photographs; Wilson, Thomas Cluff, 1907-; Yale University -- Pictorial works; Yale University -- Buildings
- Photographs, Series I
  - Trinity Church, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Elm Street (west of Church Street), circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The War Colonnade-under construction, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Old Campus, Bingham being erected, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gate between Art School and Library, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Old Campus, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Phelps Hall, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Prospect Street (north of Grove Street), circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Franklin Hall, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Gold Coast" door in Branford Court, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - High Street -looking south, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Campus and the Taft, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Grub Street" (Blount Avenue), circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bingham Hall in construction, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - United Church, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Center Church, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Old Campus in the snow, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Van-Sheff, rear, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Osborn ZoologicalLaboratory, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Franklin Hall, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Van-Sheff courtyard, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Prospect Street (north of Trumbull), circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Woolsey statue, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Saint Elmo, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Toward Wrexham Tower, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Part of Harkness Quadrangle, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The Green, circa 1926 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Minaret on Jewel Tower, Harkness, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - A court in Harkness (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Harkness Tower from the Old Campus, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - A corner of Harkness, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Wrexham Tower, Branford Court, Harkness, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Main arch, Harkness, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Linonia Court, Harkness, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Window detail in Harkness, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Winter scene in Harkness, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Memorial Colonnade and Commons, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Sheff Town - corner of Wall and College Streets, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - One of the courts in Harkness, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Corner of Branford Court, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Main arch and court -Van-Sheff, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Van-Sheff archway, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Byers Hall, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Hillhouse Avenue, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Byers Hall, Van-Sheff, St. Anthony, and Woolsey Hall from Prospect Street, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Woolsey Statue, Old Campus, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Chittenden and Harkness through Phelps Archway, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Sterling Chemistry Lab, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Sachem Hall, Prospect Street (Phi Sigma Kappa Fraternity), 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Front hall, Sachem Hall, Prospect Street, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Fireplace, Sachem Hall, Prospect Street, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 17)